<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 11/24/2013 10:24:12 PM -->
<GameData>
	<Community>
		<Row Type="CSL-BONUS-ON">
			<Value>1</Value>
		</Row>
	</Community>
	
	<Language_en_US>
		<Update>
			<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_POP_CSTATE_PROTECTED_BY" />
			<Set Text="PROTECTED BY:" />
		</Update>
		<Update>
			<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_POP_CSTATE_LABEL_CONTENDER" />
			<Set Text="CONTENDER:" />
		</Update>
		<!-- <Update>
			<Where Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_RESOURCES_TT" />
			<Set Text="These resources are in close range of the City-State&#39;s capital. All [COLOR:0:155:255:255]Strategic[ENDCOLOR] and [COLOR:205:205:0:255]Luxury[ENDCOLOR] resources will be granted to the player, when he becomes an [COLOR_CYAN]Ally[ENDCOLOR] and once the City-State connects them." />
		</Update> moved to SQL because of an apostrophe issue -->
		
		<!-- UCS compatibility -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_POPUP_UCS_MAIN_TEXT">
			<Text>Active [ICON_CITY_STATE][NEWLINE]Bonuses</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_POPUP_UCS_TOOLTIP_TITLE">
			<Text>List of active [ICON_CITY_STATE] City-States' bonuses:[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_POPUP_UCS_NO_BONUS_FOUND">
			<Text>You have currently no bonuses from [ICON_CITY_STATE] City-States.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_POPUP_UCS_NO_UCS_FOUND">
			<Text>You must enable [COLOR_YELLOW]Unique City-States[ENDCOLOR] mod to gain bonuses from [ICON_CITY_STATE] City-States.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<!-- New tags -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_POPUP_LEADER">
			<Text>{1_LeaderName} from {2_LeaderPlace}</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_POPUP_UNDER_SOI_TT">
			<Text>This City-State is under the [COLOR_CYAN]Sphere of Influence[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_POPUP_CONTENDER_INFLUENCE">
			<Text>{1_ContenderInf} [ICON_INFLUENCE] ({2_MissingInf} [ICON_INFLUENCE] to be an Ally)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_POPUP_RESOURCE_LABEL">
			<Text>RESOURCES:</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_POPUP_RESOURCE_LIST">
			<Text>{1_Icon} {2_Color}{3_Name} ({4_Amount})[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_POPUP_JERK_NO_QUESTS">
			<Text>[COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]No quests for {1_JerkTurns} turns.[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		


		<!-- Mini Civilopedia -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_ALMATY">
			<Text>Janibek Khan was a descendant of Genghis Khan and a co-founder and second Khan of the Kazakh Khanate from 1473 to 1480, following a successful rebellion against the Uzbek Khan Abu'l-Khayr Khan in 1465 and 1466.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He was a son of Barak, Khan of the Golden Horde from 1422 to 1427, who was poisoned by the emirs of the former White Horde. Barak Khan's father was Koirichak, grandson of Urus Khan, a direct descendant of Genghis Khan. Genghis Khan is Jochi Khan's father, Jochi Khan's son Tukai-Timur, Tukai-Timur's son Uz-Timur, Uz-Timur's son Khodja, Khodja's son Badakun-Uglan, Badakun-Uglan's son Urus Khan, Urus Khan's son Koirchak-khan, Koirchak-khan's son Barak Khan, and Barak Khan is Zhanibek/Janibek's father.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He led the splinter group along with Kerei, his relative, who was also a descendant of the famous Urus Khan of the White Horde. For his wisdom, he was given the title "Az", meaning "the wise" in the Kazakh language, and so was called Az-Janibek. His son, Kasym Khan, codified the laws of his people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_ANTANANARIVO">
			<Text>Ranavalona I out-maneuvered her rivals and ascended to the throne in 1829. After the death of the king Radama I, Ranavalona pursued a policy of caution with regards to foreign influence and self-sufficiency, reducing economic and political ties with European powers, repelling a French attack on the coastal town of Foulpointe, and taking vigorous measures to contain the small but growing Malagasy Christian movement initiated by members of the London Missionary Society.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]She made heavy use of the traditional practice of "fanompoana" (forced labor as tax payment) to complete public works projects and develop a standing army of Merina soldiers, whom she deployed to pacify outlying regions of the island and further expand the realm. The combination of regular warfare, disease, difficult forced labor and harsh trials by ordeal using a poisonous nut from the Tangena shrub resulted in a high mortality rate among both soldiers and civilians during her 33-year reign, with Madagascar's population reducing from 5 million in 1833 to 2.5 million in 1839.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Her policies were generally condemned and she was characterized as a tyrant at best and insane at worst. Her son, king Radama II abruptly reversed some of her policies under his reign.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_ANTWERP">
			<Text>Robert III (The Lion of Flanders) was the Count of Nevers from 1273 and Count of Flanders from 1305 until his death. He gained military fame in Italy, when he fought at the side of his father-in-law, Charles I of Sicily against the last Hohenstaufens, Manfred and Conradin. In 1270 he took part in the Eighth Crusade, led by Saint Louis. After his return from the Crusade he continued to be a loyal aid for his father, politically and militarily, in the fight against the attempts of the French King Philip IV the Fair to add Flanders to the French crown lands.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"Guy of Dampierre" broke all feudal bonds with the French king. When the resistance seemed hopeless Robert allowed himself to be taken prisoner, together with his father and his brother William of Crèvecoeur, and taken to the French King. He was locked in the castle of Chinon. He was not released until 1305, after his father had died in captivity.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The execution of the Peace Treaty of Athis-sur-Orge would mark the rule of Count Robert. However, in April 1310 he started to radically resist the French and with support of his subjects and his family he managed to make a stand against the French king. When Robert marched to Lille in 1319 the militia from Ghent refused to cross the Leie with him. When his grandson Louis I of Nevers pressured him as well, Robert gave up the battle and went to Paris in 1320 to restore feudal bonds with the French King.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_BELGRADE">
			<Text>Karadorde Petrovic was a Serbian revolutionary who led the struggle for his country's independence from the Ottoman Empire during the First Serbian Uprising of 1804-1813.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He distinguished himself during the Austro-Turkish War of 1788-1791 as a member of the Serbian Free Corps, a militia of Habsburg and Ottoman Serbs, armed and trained by the Austrians. Fearing retribution following the Austrians' and Serb rebels' defeat in 1791, he and his family fled to the Austrian Empire, where they lived until 1794.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In early 1804, following a massacre of Serb chieftains by renegade Ottoman janissaries known as Dahis, the Serbs of the Pashalik rebelled. Karadorde was unanimously elected to lead the uprising against the Dahis at an assembly of surviving chiefs. Within six months, most of the Dahi leaders had been captured and executed by Karadorde's forces. After the final remnants of Dahi resistance had been crushed, Karadorde and his followers demanded far-reaching autonomy, which Sultan Selim interpreted as the first step towards complete independence. Selim promptly declared jihad against the rebels, but by 1806, the rebels had captured all the major towns in the Pashalik, including Belgrade and Smederevo, and expelled their Muslim inhabitants. Burdened by the demands of the Russo-Turkish War of 1806-1812, Selim offered the Serbs extensive autonomy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_BOGOTA">
			<Text>Simón Bolívar (El Libertador) was a Venezuelan military and political leader who led independence movements in South America.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Bolívar was educated abroad and lived in Spain. From 1803 to 1805, Bolívar embarked on a Grand Tour that ended in Rome, where he swore to end rule of the Spanish Empire, so when their authority in the Americas weakened due to Napoleon's Peninsular War, Bolívar became a zealous combatant and politician in the Spanish American wars of independence.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Bolívar fought as a militia officer, fighting Royalist forces for the first and second Venezuelan republics and the United Provinces of New Granada. After Spanish forces subdued New Granada in 1815, Bolívar was forced into exile on Jamaica. In Haiti, Bolívar met and befriended Haitian revolutionary leader Alexandre Pétion. After promising to abolish slavery in Spanish America, Bolívar received military support from Pétion and returned to Venezuela. He established a third republic in 1817 and then crossed the Andes to liberate New Granada in 1819. Bolívar and his allies defeated the Spanish in New Granada in 1819, Venezuela and Panama in 1821, Ecuador in 1822, Peru in 1824, and Bolivia in 1825. Venezuela, New Granada, Ecuador, and Panama were merged into the Republic of Colombia (Gran Colombia), with Bolívar as president.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_BRATISLAVA">
			<Text>Svatopluk I governed a principality within Moravia and later became a ruler of Great Moravia, which attained its maximum territorial expansion during his reign (870-871, 871-894).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In 870 Svatopluk dethroned Rastislav, who was a vassal of Louis the German, and betrayed him to the Franks, who also imprisoned Svatopluk. After the Moravians rebelled against the Franks, Svatopluk was released and led the rebels to victory over the invaders. Although he was obliged to pay tribute to East Francia under the peace treaty concluded at Forchheim (Germany) in 874, he was able to expand his territories outside the Franks' sphere of interest in the following years. His forces even invaded the March of Pannonia within East Francia in 882.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Svatopluk established a good relationship with the popes, and he and his people were formally taken under the protection of the Holy See in 880. Pope Stephen V even addressed him as "King" in a letter written in 885. Svatopluk seems to have wanted to appease the German clergy who opposed the conducting of the liturgy in Old Church Slavonic, and he expelled the disciples of Methodius from Moravia in 886, after their teacher's death.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Not long after his death Svatopluk's realm of Great Moravia collapsed in the midst of a power struggle between his sons and the intensifying Hungarian raids.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_BRUSSELS">
			<Text>Albert I was King of the Belgians from 23 December 1909 until his death in 1934. He ruled during an eventful period in the history of Belgium, which included the period of World War I (1914-1918), when most of Belgium was occupied by German forces, adoption of the Treaty of Versailles in June 1919, the ruling of the Belgian Congo as an overseas possession of Belgium along with the League of Nations mandate of Ruanda-Urundi, the reconstruction of Belgium following the war, and the first five years of the Great Depression (1929-1934).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He is popularly referred to as the "Knight King" or "Soldier King" in Belgium in reference to his role during World War I. At its end, as a commander of the Army Group Flanders, consisting of Belgian, British and French divisions, Albert led the final offensive of the war that liberated occupied Belgium.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In 1925 Albert founded Africa's first national park, now known as Virunga National Park, in what is now Democratic Republic of Congo. During this period, he was also the first reigning European monarch to visit the United States.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Albert died in a mountaineering accident in eastern Belgium in 1934, at the age of 58, and he was succeeded by his son Leopold III. There are still some conspiracy theories about his death, that questioned the official version and suggested that the King was murdered (or even committed suicide).</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_BUCHAREST">
			<Text>Vlad III (the Impaler, Dracula) was Voivode and the most important ruler in Wallachian history, and a national hero of Romania.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Vlad was held as a hostage in the Ottoman Empire in 1442 to secure their father's loyalty. After John Hunyadi, regent-governor of Hungary, invaded Wallachia in 1447, Vlad tried to regain his position with help of the Ottomans, but unsuccessfully. In 1456 he invaded Wallachia, this time with Hungarian support to replace his cousin on the throne. Then he began a purge among the boyars to strengthen his position and he also came into conflict with the Transylvanian Saxons, who supported his opponents, taking the captured people to Wallachia, where he had them impaled.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]When the Ottoman Sultan, Mehmed II, ordered Vlad to pay homage, Vlad had captured and impaled his envoys. In 1462, he attacked Ottoman territory, massacring tens of thousands of Turks and Muslim Bulgarians. Mehmed launched a campaign against Wallachia to replace Vlad, but soon fleed from assassination. Vlad seeked an assistance from Matthias Corvinus, King of Hungary, but Corvinus had him imprisoned.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Vlad was held in captivity in Visegrád from 1463 to 1475 and he was released at the request of Stephen III of Moldavia. He was killed in battle during fights in Corvinus' army against the Ottomans in Bosnia.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_BUDAPEST">
			<Text>Stephen I, also known as King Saint Stephen, was the last Grand Prince of the Hungarians, and the first King of Hungary, until his death in 1038. Although both of his parents were baptized, Stephen was the first member of his family to become a devout Christian.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He was crowned in 1000 or 1001 with a crown sent by Pope Sylvester II. He protected the independence of his kingdom by forcing the invading troops of Conrad II, Holy Roman Emperor, to withdraw from Hungary in 1030.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Stephen established at least one archbishopric, six bishoprics and three Benedictine monasteries, leading the Church in Hungary to develop independently from the archbishops of the Holy Roman Empire. His system of local administration was based on counties organized around fortresses and administered by royal officials. Hungary enjoyed a lasting period of peace during his reign, and became a preferred route for pilgrims and merchants traveling between Western Europe, the Holy Land and Constantinople.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]His death was followed by civil wars which lasted for decades. He was canonized by Pope Gregory VII, together with his son, Emeric, and Bishop Gerard of Csanád, in 1083. In Hungary, his feast day (celebrated on 20 August) is also a public holiday commemorating the foundation of the state, known as State Foundation Day.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_BUENOS_AIRES">
			<Text>Eva Perón also called Evita, was an Argentine politician, activist, actress, and philanthropist who served as First Lady of Argentina.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In 1934, at the age of 15, she moved to the nation's capital of Buenos Aires to pursue a career as a stage, radio, and film actress. She met Colonel Juan Perón in 1944, married him the following year and in 1946 when he was elected President of Argentina she became a powerful within the pro-Peronist trade unions, primarily for speaking on behalf of labor rights. She also ran the Ministries of Labor and Health, founded and ran the charitable "Eva Perón Foundation", championed women's suffrage in Argentina, and founded and ran the nation's first large-scale female political party, the Female Peronist Party.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In 1951, Eva Perón announced her candidacy for the Peronist nomination for the office of Vice President of Argentina, receiving great support from the Peronist political base, low-income and working-class Argentines who were referred to as "descamisados". Opposition coupled with her declining health and ultimately forced her to withdraw her candidacy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In 1952, shortly before her death from cancer at 33, Eva Perón was given the title of "Spiritual Leader of the Nation" by the Argentine Congress. She was given a state funeral upon her death, a prerogative generally reserved for heads of state.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_BYBLOS">
			<Text>Ahiram himself is not titled a king, neither of Byblos nor of any other city state. It is said that he was succeeded by his son Ithobaal I who is the first to be explicitly entitled King of Byblos, which is due to an old misreading of a text lacuna. According to a new reconstruction of the lacuna the name of Ahiram's son is to be read [Pil]sibaal, and the reading Ithobaal should be disregarded. The early king list of Byblos is again subject to further study.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Ahiram is now mostly known of his sarcophagus, discovered in 1923 by the French excavator Pierre Montet in tomb V of the royal necropolis of Byblos.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The sarcophagus is famed for its bas relief carvings, and its Phoenician inscription. One of five known Byblian royal inscriptions, the inscription is considered to be the earliest known example of the fully developed Phoenician alphabet. The Phoenician alphabet is believed to be the parent alphabet for a wide number of the world's current writing systems; including the Greek, Latin and Cyrillic Alphabets, and the Hebrew, Arabic and Urdu Abjads. For some scholars it represents the terminus post quem of the transmission of the alphabet to Europe.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Ahiram is not attested in any other Ancient Oriental source, although some scholars have suggested a possible connection to the contemporary King Hiram mentioned in the Hebrew Bible.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_CAHOKIA">
			<Text>Tuskaloosa (died 1540) was a paramount chief of a Mississippian chiefdom in what is now the U.S. state of Alabama. His people were possibly ancestors to the several southern Native American confederacies (the Choctaw and Creek peoples) who later emerged in the region.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Tuskaloosa is notable for leading the Battle of Mabila at his fortified village against the Spanish conquistador Hernando de Soto. After being taken hostage by the Spanish as they passed through his territory, Tuskaloosa organized a surprise attack on his captors at Mabila, but was ultimately defeated.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Contemporary records describe the paramount chief as being very tall and well built, with some of the chroniclers saying Tuaskaloosa stood a foot and a half taller than the Spaniards. His name, derived from the western Muskogean language elements tashka and losa, means "Black Warrior".[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]"His appearance was full of dignity; he was tall of person, muscular, lean, and symmetrical. He was the suzerain of many territories, and of numerous people, being equally feared by his vassals and the neighbouring nations" - wrote Hernando De Soto in 1557.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The modern city of Tuscaloosa, Alabama, is named for him.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_CAPE_TOWN">
			<Text>Johan "Jan" van Riebeeck was a Dutch navigator and colonial administrator of the Dutch East India Company (DEIC).[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He was head of the DEIC trading post in Tonkin, Indochina. After being dismissed from that position in 1645, he began to advocate a refreshment station in the Cape of Good Hope. DEIC finally requested him to undertake the command of the initial settlement in the future South Africa. He landed three ships in Table Bay, at the future Cape Town site in 1652.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Van Riebeeck was Commander of the Cape from 1652 to 1662. He was charged with building a fort named Fort de Goede Hoop ("Fort of Good Hope"), with improving the natural anchorage at Table Bay, planting cereals, fruit and vegetables, and obtaining livestock from the indigenous Khoi people. Fort was made of mud, clay, and timber and was later replaced by the Castle of Good Hope, built between 1666 and 1679 after van Riebeeck had left the Cape.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Jan van Riebeeck died in Batavia (Jakarta) on Java in 1677. He is of immense cultural and historical significance to South Africa, as he was in particular during the Apartheid era. Many Afrikaners view him as the founding father of their nation. Consequently, his image appeared ubiquitously on stamps and bank notes issued until 1994. The coat of arms of the city of Cape Town is based on the van Riebeeck family coat of arms.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_COLOMBO">
			<Text>Don Stephen Senanayake was a Ceylonese statesman. He was the first Prime Minister of Ceylon having emerged as the leader of the Sri Lankan independence movement that led to the establishment of self-rule in Ceylon. He is considered as the "Father of the Nation".[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Born to an entrepreneur from the village of Botale, Senanayake was educated at S. Thomas' College, Mutwal before briefly working as a clerk in the Surveyor General's Department. Joining the family business, he managed the family own estates and the Kahatagaha Graphite Mine. Long with his brothers, Senanayake became active in the temperance movement which grew into the independence movement following 1915 Sinhalese-Muslim riots, in which the Senanayake brothers were imprisoned without charges for 46 days.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He was elected unopposed in 1924 to the Legislative Council of Ceylon from Negombo, becoming the Secretary of the unofficial members group of the Legislative Council. In 1931, he was elected to the State Council of Ceylon, where he served as Minister of Agriculture and Lands, and later to the first Parliament of Ceylon where he served as a Prime Minister from 1947 until his death in 1952.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]D.S. Senanayake is respected by Sinhalese and some Muslims, but not by the Tamils who were disenfranchised virtually by his citizenship laws.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_FLORENCE">
			<Text>Lorenzo di Piero de' Medici, known as Lorenzo the Magnificent was an Italian statesman, banker, de facto ruler of the Florentine Republic, and the most powerful and enthusiastic patron of Renaissance culture in Italy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He was a magnate, diplomat, politician and patron of scholars, artists, and poets. As a patron, he is best known for his sponsorship of artists such as Botticelli and Michelangelo. He held the balance of power within the Italic League, an alliance of states that stabilized political conditions on the Italian peninsula for decades, and his life coincided with the mature phase of the Italian Renaissance and the Golden Age of Florence.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]On the foreign policy front, Lorenzo manifested a clear plan to stem the territorial ambitions of Pope Sixtus IV, in the name of the balance of the Italian League of 1454. For these reasons, Lorenzo was the subject of the Pazzi conspiracy (1478), in which his brother Giuliano was assassinated.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Peace of Lodi of 1454 that he supported among the various Italian states collapsed with his death. He is buried in the Medici Chapel in Florence.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]His second son, Giovanni, who became Pope Leo X, retook the city in 1512 with the aid of a Spanish army and Papal troops. Giulio de' Medici, a nephew of Lorenzo, also became a Pope of the Catholic Church, Clement VII.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_GENEVA">
			<Text>John Calvin was a French theologian, pastor and reformer during the Protestant Reformation. He was a principal figure in the development of Calvinism.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Calvinist doctrines were influenced by and elaborated upon the Augustinian and other Christian traditions. Various Congregational, Reformed and Presbyterian churches, which look to Calvin as the chief expositor of their beliefs, have spread throughout the world.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Calvin was originally trained as a humanist lawyer. He broke from the Roman Catholic Church around 1530. After religious tensions erupted in widespread deadly violence against Protestant Christians in France, Calvin fled to Basel, Switzerland, where in 1536 he published the first edition of the Institutes. In that same year, Calvin was recruited by Frenchman William Farel to join the Reformation in Geneva. However, the governing council of the city resisted the implementation of their ideas, so they were expelled. He proceeded to Strasbourg, where he became the minister of a church of French refugees.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He continued to support the reform movement in Geneva, and in 1541 he was invited back to lead the church of the city. Following his return, Calvin introduced new forms of church government and liturgy, despite the strong opposition. During this period. Calvin spent his final years promoting the Reformation both in Geneva and throughout Europe.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_GENOA">
			<Text>Andrea Doria, Prince of Melfi was a Genoese statesman, condottiero, and admiral, who played a key role in the Republic of Genoa during his lifetime.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In September 1528 Andrea Doria and his forces drove the French out of Genoa and were triumphantly received by the city. As the ruler of Genoa, Doria reformed the Republic's constitution in an aristocratic sense, eliminating the factions that had plagued the republic in the past centuries. He refused offers to take the lordship of Genoa and even the dogeship, but accepted the position of "perpetual censor".[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Originally elected for life, the Doge's office was reduced to two years. At the same time plebeians were declared ineligible, and the appointment of the doge was entrusted to the members of the great and the little councils. His reformed constitution of the Republic of Genoa would last until the end of the republic in 1797.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]From 1528 until his death, Doria exercised a predominant influence in the councils of the Genoese republic. He is also considered the foremost naval leader of his time.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Several ships were named in honour of the admiral, the most famous being the Italian passenger liner SS Andrea Doria, launched in 1951, which sank following a collision in 1956.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_HANOI">
			<Text>Lý Thái To, was a founding emperor of Lý dynasty and the 6th ruler of Dai Viet, who reigned from 1009 to 1028.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In 1010 he decided to relocate the capital from Hoa Lu to the site of Dai La (modern-day Hanoi), earlier capital in the rich Red River Delta. The outer regions beyond the Lý heartland, were in the hands of families allied with the Lý family by marriage.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Lý Thái To abandoned a scheme of dividing the plain into "ten circuits" and replaced it with 24 routes. which resembled a naturally Southeast Asian mandala system.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In 1011, Lý Thái To raised an army and attacked rebels in the southern provinces, in what is now Thanh Hoá and Nghe An. He campaigned there for two years, burning villages and capturing local leaders. While returning by sea in 1012, a great storm threatened to sink his boat, which he understood as a divine judgment upon him for the violence he had brought upon so many people. In 1013-1015, Lý Thái To sent soldiers into the northern mountains of modern Hà Giang Province to pacify Hani people who allied with the Dali Kingdom in Yunnan.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Having begun life as a Buddhist monk, Lý Thái To practiced Buddhism and promoted it as the national religion. He gave much support to the Buddhist clergy and institutions and donated money to build pagodas throughout Dai Viet.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_HONG_KONG">
			<Text>Sir Kai Ho, born Ho Shan-kai, was a Hong Kong barrister, physician and essayist in Colonial Hong Kong. He played a key role in the relationship between the Hong Kong local community and the British colonial government.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In 1882 he embarked on changing the landscape of Hong Kong's colleges and universities. Sir Kai not only gained the people's acceptance, but also helped the British make possible a number of health-related establishments that otherwise would have been misunderstood by the public. In 1887, the Hong Kong College of Medicine for Chinese was opened. He made it an initiative that Chinese medicine practitioners too could benefit from an institution that focused on Western medicine. This College later became the basis from which the University of Hong Kong was established in 1910.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]He is remembered as a supporter of the Reform Movement and as a teacher of Sun Yat-sen. Throughout his lifetime, he was a vocal supporter for Sun Yat-sen and his revolution to overthrow China's Manchu-led Qing dynasty. A prolific critic of the Self-Strengthening Movement, Ho advocated China to follow the British system in developing constitutional monarchy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Kai Tak Airport, was named after him in 1914, long before the idea of an aerodrome was first mentioned in 1925.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_IFE">
			<Text>Oduduwa was a Yoruba divine king, legendary founder of the Ife Empire and a creator deity (orisha) in the Yoruba religion.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]According to tradition, he was the holder of the title of the Olofin of Ile-Ife, the Yoruba holy city. He ruled briefly in Ife, and also served as the progenitor of a number of independent royal dynasties in Yorubaland.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In Yoruba religious traditions, Oduduwa is seen as a divine or semi-divine being that was sent by the creator deity, Olodumare, from heaven to create the earth upon the waters. These beliefs are held by Yoruba traditionalists to be the cornerstone of their story of creation. In this narrative, Oduduwa is also known as Olofin Otete, the one who took the Basket of Existence from Olodumare. Historical accounts hold that he migrated intot the Ife valley from Oke Ora, a community to Ife's east. The time and length of his reign are not certain, but Yoruba spirituality believes that Oduduwa is believed to be as old as time itself.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Oduduwa was the first ruler of a unified Ife, which before him had existed as a group of loosely allied communities of thirteen Elu. He is also the founding father of various independent royal dynasties in Yorubaland, and is today venerated as "the hero, the warrior, the leader, and the father of the Yoruba race." </Text>
		</Row>
		<!--<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CSL_LEADER_SHORT_MINOR_CIV_">
			<Text></Text>
		</Row>-->
		
		
		
		<!-- Personality texts -->
		<!-- First meeting texts (7) -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_FRIENDLY_1">
			<Text>Greetings, great leader. We represent [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. We hope that we can forge a strong and lasting peace with your mighty empire.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_FRIENDLY_2">
			<Text>Welcome to [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]! We have been awaiting a strong ally like you for a long time!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_FRIENDLY_3">
			<Text>Pleased to meet you. Welcome to the benevolent state of [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. We look forward to sharing our knowledge with you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_FRIENDLY_4">
			<Text>Hallelujah! We have heard about your mighty empire in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. Make yourself at home.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_FRIENDLY_5">
			<Text>Greetings from [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]! We look forward to creating a strong partnership with your people!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_FRIENDLY_6">
			<Text>Come in! We have heard many stories about you. We are glad you visited [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_FRIENDLY_7">
			<Text>Nice to see such a mighty ruler in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. We hope you have big plans for us!</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_NEUTRAL_1">
			<Text>Greetings. We are the people of [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. Treat us fairly and we shall have peace.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_NEUTRAL_2">
			<Text>Hello passerby. You have entered the territory of [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. We do not want any trouble.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_NEUTRAL_3">
			<Text>Good day. The nation of [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] welcomes new acquaintances. Be kind and we will be happy to return the favor.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_NEUTRAL_4">
			<Text>Greetings, stranger. What are you looking for in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_NEUTRAL_5">
			<Text>Hello! We did not expect any guests in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. What we can do for you?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_NEUTRAL_6">
			<Text>Welcome! We can see you are very tired after the long journey to [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. Can we do something for you?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_NEUTRAL_7">
			<Text>Greetings, traveler. How did you find [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]? We have avoided outside contact so far.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_HOSTILE_1">
			<Text>Halt, Stranger! We are the mighty people of [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. Trifle with us at your own peril!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_HOSTILE_2">
			<Text>Careful! Do not try to start a war with [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. We know how to defend our people!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_HOSTILE_3">
			<Text>Don't move, stranger! We heard many stories about your kind in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_HOSTILE_4">
			<Text>Mhmmm, so you say that you want to be friends with [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR], huh? That's very nice of you, but we don't trust strangers!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_HOSTILE_5">
			<Text>What a coincidence! Our fortune-teller foresaw the coming of the end of the world. Is this your purpose in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_HOSTILE_6">
			<Text>Well, well. We think you have no interest in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_HOSTILE_7">
			<Text>Oh, gods! That's just what we needed! A bloodthirsty tyrant in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_IRRATIONAL_1">
			<Text>We are the ones who knock, but now you are first, so I guess we are not the only ones, so... nevermind. Welcome to [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_IRRATIONAL_2">
			<Text>Gods send us a Prophet! Let the people of [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] be grateful for such a gift!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_IRRATIONAL_3">
			<Text>Really?! Are you supposed to be our master? We don't think [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] needs any. But we can talk about that, right?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_IRRATIONAL_4">
			<Text>We wondered why scouts are not visiting [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR], such a beautiful country... Then we thought that we are not that great... And now there's you. What to do? Huh, what to do...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_IRRATIONAL_5">
			<Text>Are you the star that hit the ground yesterday? We saw that and all people of [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] were waiting for your visit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_IRRATIONAL_6">
			<Text>Why [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] should even look at you? Do you think you are the special one? What makes you better than us? Clothes? Weapons? There many more things, and we can teach you to look beyond your plain imagination.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_IRRATIONAL_7">
			<Text>Oh, oh, finally! We looked for someone to help [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] in our troubles. Everyone has troubles, but we have the serious troubles. Do you know what serious troubles are? Ah, no? Then you will...</Text>
		</Row>


		<!-- Trait texts (7) -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_CULTURED_1">
			<Text>Different cultures can always benefit from each other.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_CULTURED_2">
			<Text>Please, get to know our culture. It's important to us.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_CULTURED_3">
			<Text>We can start a cultural revolution in your country!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_CULTURED_4">
			<Text>We are interested in exchanging some cultural artifacts. Do you have some?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_CULTURED_5">
			<Text>Every culture is interesting. We want to know more about yours, too.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_CULTURED_6">
			<Text>Strong culture is the key to victory! And you do want to conquest the world, right?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_CULTURED_7">
			<Text>We want you to adopt our culture. Are you ok with that?</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MILITARISTIC_1">
			<Text>We have great military knowledge. We can increase the strength of your army.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MILITARISTIC_2">
			<Text>Glorious battles are our way of life!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MILITARISTIC_3">
			<Text>We can train special units for you. Come and check them out!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MILITARISTIC_4">
			<Text>We studied the art of war. We can teach you some unique techniques.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MILITARISTIC_5">
			<Text>How about we start a war?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MILITARISTIC_6">
			<Text>We heard you trained the greatest army in the world. We kind of like it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MILITARISTIC_7">
			<Text>Sometimes, war is pointless. But sometimes, it's the only option.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MARITIME_1">
			<Text>We can help accelerate your civilization&apos;s growth.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MARITIME_2">
			<Text>We can provide enough food to feed your people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MARITIME_3">
			<Text>We can see that your people are starving! We can help them.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MARITIME_4">
			<Text>We had good harvests this year, and we can share some resources with you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MARITIME_5">
			<Text>Do you want to look at our food reserves?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MARITIME_6">
			<Text>We like exchanging things. We can provide you as much food as you want.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MARITIME_7">
			<Text>Check our fruits! Taste our vegetables! Smell our fish! Enjoy our spices!</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MERCANTILE_1">
			<Text>We have many luxuries that can make your citizens happy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MERCANTILE_2">
			<Text>Our riches can shame any mighty leader.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MERCANTILE_3">
			<Text>If you are looking for luxuries, then you came to the right place!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MERCANTILE_4">
			<Text>We have enough gold to make anyone happy. Even a leader like you!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MERCANTILE_5">
			<Text>Luxuries, luxuries, and once more, luxuries! That's the key to co-existence.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MERCANTILE_6">
			<Text>The only thing that makes people happy is money. Anyone who denies that is a fool.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_MERCANTILE_7">
			<Text>Our guilds, banks, mints, and markets make dreams possible. What are your dreams?</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_RELIGIOUS_1">
			<Text>We can help nurture your religious traditions.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_RELIGIOUS_2">
			<Text>Pray in our temples, and maybe the gods will forgive your sins!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_RELIGIOUS_3">
			<Text>If you are looking for forgiveness, then you came to the right place. Pray and repent.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_RELIGIOUS_4">
			<Text>Our sacred places are open for your people and anyone else who wants to pray.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_RELIGIOUS_5">
			<Text>We can speak with the gods! Remember that!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_RELIGIOUS_6">
			<Text>We are the religious capital of the world. Anyone who denies that is a heretic and must be burned at the stake!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_GREETING_RELIGIOUS_7">
			<Text>Are you here to confess your sins?</Text>
		</Row>

		
		<!-- Bonus texts (7) -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_GOLD_1">
			<Text>We amassed some gold in our treasury. {1_Value} [ICON_GOLD] Gold for you from our nation.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_GOLD_2">
			<Text>Everyone needs money! Take this {1_Value} [ICON_GOLD] Gold and go!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_GOLD_3">
			<Text>This {1_Value} [ICON_GOLD] Gold should help you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_GOLD_4">
			<Text>Please, use this {1_Value} [ICON_GOLD] Gold wisely!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_GOLD_5">
			<Text>Don't forget to take {1_Value} [ICON_GOLD] Gold!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_GOLD_6">
			<Text>We want to gift you {1_Value} [ICON_GOLD] Gold.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_GOLD_7">
			<Text>We are in a good mood. {1_Value} [ICON_GOLD] Gold for you!</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_CULTURE_1">
			<Text>We want to give you a piece of treasured art worth {1_Value} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_CULTURE_2">
			<Text>Our cultural artifacts will be a nice addition to your empire. We lay {1_Value} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture onto your hands.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_CULTURE_3">
			<Text>{1_Value} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture is everything we have right now in our museums.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_CULTURE_4">
			<Text>Admire our art! This {1_Value} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture is yours now.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_CULTURE_5">
			<Text>We sculpted {1_Value} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for you. Present it to your people!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_CULTURE_6">
			<Text>We have some spare {1_Value} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture for you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_CULTURE_7">
			<Text>This {1_Value} [ICON_CULTURE] Culture should change your attitude toward us.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FOOD_1">
			<Text>Take this cart filled with {1_Value} [ICON_FOOD] Food to boost your developement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FOOD_2">
			<Text>These containers with {1_Value} [ICON_FOOD] Food are for your people. Feed them.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FOOD_3">
			<Text>Fresh {1_Value} [ICON_FOOD] Food from our market is available for you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FOOD_4">
			<Text>Do you like local meals? {1_Value} [ICON_FOOD] Food is prepared for you to taste.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FOOD_5">
			<Text>Maybe this {1_Value} [ICON_FOOD] Food will strengthen our relationship?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FOOD_6">
			<Text>We've transported containers with {1_Value} [ICON_FOOD] Food to your civilization.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FOOD_7">
			<Text>{1_Value} [ICON_FOOD] Food is at your disposal. Share it with your people!</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FAITH_1">
			<Text>Our religious artifacts are worth {1_Value} [ICON_PEACE] Faith. Take them, please.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FAITH_2">
			<Text>The gods have sent you {1_Value} [ICON_PEACE] Faith!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FAITH_3">
			<Text>Our prophets pleased the gods, and they sent you {1_Value} [ICON_PEACE] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FAITH_4">
			<Text>Please, take this sacred cross worth {1_Value} [ICON_PEACE] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FAITH_5">
			<Text>We see a dim future for your civilization. Maybe this {1_Value} [ICON_PEACE] Faith will help guide you toward enlightenment.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FAITH_6">
			<Text>The gods decided to send you {1_Value} [ICON_PEACE] Faith. Appreciate their kindness!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_FAITH_7">
			<Text>We put in a word for you. The gods listened and transferred {1_Value} [ICON_PEACE] Faith.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_UNIT_1">
			<Text>We trained a [COLOR_CYAN]{1_Value}[ENDCOLOR] for you. Use his abilities wisely.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_UNIT_2">
			<Text>A [COLOR_CYAN]{1_Value}[ENDCOLOR] from our camp wants to join you. He is ready for your orders now.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_UNIT_3">
			<Text>A fresh recruit for you: a [COLOR_CYAN]{1_Value}[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_UNIT_4">
			<Text>What about hiring one of our best [COLOR_CYAN]{1_Value}s[ENDCOLOR]?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_UNIT_5">
			<Text>We want to join your coalition. Take this [COLOR_CYAN]{1_Value}[ENDCOLOR]. We would like to show you our devotion!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_UNIT_6">
			<Text>[COLOR_CYAN]{1_Value}s[ENDCOLOR] can be very useful. We prepared one for you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_FIRST_CONTACT_BONUS_UNIT_7">
			<Text>We heard you need a [COLOR_CYAN]{1_Value}[ENDCOLOR]. We can provide you with one!</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		<!-- Greeting texts (when not first) (8) -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_FRIENDLY_1">
			<Text>Welcome! Your appearance in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] amazed us! Become our friend, please!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_FRIENDLY_2">
			<Text>We are pleased to meet you! Unfortunately, we did not expect anybody in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR], and we have nothing prepared as a gift. Forgive us!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_FRIENDLY_3">
			<Text>Welcome to [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_FRIENDLY_4">
			<Text>Greetings, mighty leader. You are in the best place in the world - [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. It's a shame we cannot give you anything.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_FRIENDLY_5">
			<Text>What a wonderful day! Welcome to [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]! You should have announced your arrival. We weren't prepared.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_FRIENDLY_6">
			<Text>Praise the day! Welcome to [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]! We would have made some preparations, if only we knew...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_FRIENDLY_7">
			<Text>Praise the gods! We doubted anyone would ever arrive to [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. We spent everything we had to survive those harsh times.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_FRIENDLY_8">
			<Text>What a surprise! We're sincerely sorry we cannot give you anything. Please, feel welcome in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_NEUTRAL_1">
			<Text>Greetings. We have nothing for you. Walk away from [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_NEUTRAL_2">
			<Text>Hi. Friendship with [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] is all you can afford for now. Appreciate it!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_NEUTRAL_3">
			<Text>Hello. You entered [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. Be careful, we do not want any trouble.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_NEUTRAL_4">
			<Text>Hi! You have nothing for [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR], so we have nothing for you, either!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_NEUTRAL_5">
			<Text>Good day. What are you looking for in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_NEUTRAL_6">
			<Text>How do you do? Do you like [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_NEUTRAL_7">
			<Text>How are you doing? Travel through [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR], and we will change your attitude toward our nation.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_NEUTRAL_8">
			<Text>Good morning, stranger. We want to tell you that [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] is not eager to be involved in any conflict.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_HOSTILE_1">
			<Text>Hi. Don't think you get anything from [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR].</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_HOSTILE_2">
			<Text>Halt! Turn away from [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]! We won't give you anything!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_HOSTILE_3">
			<Text>Don't move! You are trespassing in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]! Turn around and go away!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_HOSTILE_4">
			<Text>Huh, another usurper. What do you want from [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_HOSTILE_5">
			<Text>Well, well! Do you expect [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] to kneel before you?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_HOSTILE_6">
			<Text>Two steps back! We have orders to kill anyone approaching [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. Do you want to die?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_HOSTILE_7">
			<Text>Who are you? We did not expect anyone in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. It would be better if you go away.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_HOSTILE_8">
			<Text>Who told you about [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]? We will kill them!</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_IRRATIONAL_1">
			<Text>What should we do with you, huh? There were rumours about a mighty ruler, but are you the one? Would such a person visit [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_IRRATIONAL_2">
			<Text>We don't know if we should kill you or spare your life... Though decision... Normally [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] does not tolerate unexpected visits.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_IRRATIONAL_3">
			<Text>We meet new people every day. We killed many of those who had not fullfiled the standards of [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. Are you the one?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_IRRATIONAL_4">
			<Text>To be, or not to be? These are the questions we ask in [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR]. Can you help us to resolve this old dilemma?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_IRRATIONAL_5">
			<Text>Oh, are you back? We thought you left [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] yesterday? Ah! You are not the one we thought you are. Sorry, you are so similar...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_IRRATIONAL_6">
			<Text>Many civilizations will turn into ashes until [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR] finds someone of a godd will. Don't pretend to be the chosen one!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_IRRATIONAL_7">
			<Text>Welcome to [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR], where we feed you and talk about great things. Unless you try to deceive us... Then we will kill you without any hesitation. Be warned!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_FRIENDSHIP_IRRATIONAL_8">
			<Text>Go away! Too many people tried to deceive us thinking we are vulnerable... We, [COLOR_CYAN]{1_civ}[ENDCOLOR], are only a small nation. We do great things. We help each other. Don't try to destroy that like the others!</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		<!-- Nothing -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_MINOR_CIV_CONTACT_BONUS_NOTHING_1">
			<Text>Just nothing.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		
		<!-- Visit texts (10) -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_PROTECTED_1">
			<Text>Here comes our protector! May the gods will be with you!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_PROTECTED_2">
			<Text>Greetings, our saviour! What we can do for your nation?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_PROTECTED_3">
			<Text>Hello, our friend! Everything alright with our agreement?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_PROTECTED_4">
			<Text>Welcome again, mighty ruler! We are happy to see you so powerful!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_PROTECTED_5">
			<Text>The gods have sent you to us! We are safe now!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_PROTECTED_6">
			<Text>Welcome again! Long time no see. Do you want to continue our agreement?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_PROTECTED_7">
			<Text>Greetings! It's been a while since you offered your protection. Our people are frightened by local neighbours!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_PROTECTED_8">
			<Text>Good to see you again! We have peace and prosperity under your wings!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_PROTECTED_9">
			<Text>Hello again, protector! We have thought about a wider coalition with our neighbours. You could visit them, too.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_PROTECTED_10">
			<Text>Ha! We knew you would come soon! And no one believed us. Your protection saves our lives!</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_FRIENDLY_1">
			<Text>We're happy to see you again! What we can do for you?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_FRIENDLY_2">
			<Text>Hello again! What brings you to us?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_FRIENDLY_3">
			<Text>Greetings! We hope that our relationship is in its best condition. Can we do something for you?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_FRIENDLY_4">
			<Text>Good to see you! Do you want to talk?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_FRIENDLY_5">
			<Text>What a coincidence! We wanted to talk with you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_FRIENDLY_6">
			<Text>Long time no see. Have you managed to fulfill our requests?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_FRIENDLY_7">
			<Text>Hello, how are you? Today is a good day to talk.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_FRIENDLY_8">
			<Text>Nice to see you! Do you want something to eat? You seem exhausted. Tell us what happened.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_FRIENDLY_9">
			<Text>Goodness, you look like a ghost! What happened? Can we help you somehow?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_FRIENDLY_10">
			<Text>Brothers and sisters, we welcome you again! What do you need?</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_NEUTRAL_1">
			<Text>Hello. What brought you here again?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_NEUTRAL_2">
			<Text>Good day, wise ruler. Do you want something from us?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_NEUTRAL_3">
			<Text>Hello again. We do not want any trouble. What brings you to our city?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_NEUTRAL_4">
			<Text>Hello. We do what we must. Do you?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_NEUTRAL_5">
			<Text>Greetings. What brings such a mighty ruler to our city?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_NEUTRAL_6">
			<Text>Hi. I suppose you need something, again...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_NEUTRAL_7">
			<Text>Greetings. After your latest deeds, we are not sure we want to cooperate with you. This may bring more trouble to us!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_NEUTRAL_8">
			<Text>Huh, you again. Our neighbours do not trust you. Why should we?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_NEUTRAL_9">
			<Text>Good morning. How are you? Your presence here is questioned. What do you want from us this time?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_NEUTRAL_10">
			<Text>Oh, my lord. I thought we understood each other last time. Do we need to explain everything to you again?</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_HOSTILE_1">
			<Text>Arghh, it's you again! We hoped we would never see you again.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_HOSTILE_2">
			<Text>Oh, it's you. Don't forget our relationship hasn't changed since our last meeting.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_HOSTILE_3">
			<Text>Well, well. Do you need something from us? Again?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_HOSTILE_4">
			<Text>Huh! You want some help from us? Forget it!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_HOSTILE_5">
			<Text>Stop! We warned you once! Next time, we will kill you!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_HOSTILE_6">
			<Text>Warning! You are stepping into a restricted area! Identify yourself!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_HOSTILE_7">
			<Text>You are not welcome here! What do you want?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_HOSTILE_8">
			<Text>We've been building an army to protect our people from you.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_HOSTILE_9">
			<Text>Don't move! We told you to not to show yourself here!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_HOSTILE_10">
			<Text>We thought we could work together. How wrong we were! Begone!</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_IRRATIONAL_1">
			<Text>We are not in the mood to talk with you, right now. Maybe tomorrow. Maybe never.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_IRRATIONAL_2">
			<Text>Ah! It's you again! It's always good to see you. We were about to bring up a subject, but... what was that!?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_IRRATIONAL_3">
			<Text>Uh-oh, what are you doing here today?! Weren't we arranged for tomorrow? Hmm... Seems we need to change our plans then, right?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_IRRATIONAL_4">
			<Text>We love meetings like this one. We can chitchat a bit. We are friends, right? Maybe yesterday we wanted to backstab you, but, you know, it was one of those days where we hated everyone on the planet. Including you and even God itself.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_IRRATIONAL_5">
			<Text>Maybe at least once you could announce your arrival?! Don't you think other people have some personal business too, huh?! Selfish bastard...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_IRRATIONAL_6">
			<Text>It's good to see you! Sit down, please. Maybe wine? Steak? We were about to serve a meal, and there's always one additional seat for an unexpected guest, and it seems that's you today! Tell us, what do you want?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_IRRATIONAL_7">
			<Text>We know you want to discover our secrets, but not this time. Tell us what do you need and go away keeping yours!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_IRRATIONAL_8">
			<Text>Can you see that Moon? Can you read the signs? No? Huh, that's very bad...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_IRRATIONAL_9">
			<Text>One man comes, another leaves us. This is how it's always been for us. Will you be the former or the latter?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_STATE_DIPLO_HELLO_PEACE_IRRATIONAL_10">
			<Text>When we look at you, we get a strange feeling... Our astrologer should be able to say more about it, would you like to know more?</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>
